Amin Razavi

■ +989360705198 | **Mainter Mainter Mainter Mainter** | **Mainter Mainter** | **Mainter** | **Ma**

Personal Profile ____

A Bachelor's student at the University of Tehran, with 2+ years of experience in full-stack development in **Dybug** company. Primarily, interested in Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence and Data Mining. Now, actively looking for research opportunities as either an MSc or a PhD student.

Education

University of Tehran (Best university of Iran generally and in computer science field)

Tehran, Iran

Bachelor of computer science

Sept 2018 - Current

• GPA: 3.26/4

Iranian University Entrance Exam(Konkur)

Tehran, Iran

Before bachelor

July 2018

• Rank: 388 among 144437 applicants

Alavi Tehran, Iran

High School Sept 2014 - July 2018

• **GPA:** 19.85/20

Scholarships And Certifications

Scholarship for study as a bachelor student from University of Tehran

2 years Scholarship for rank of Iranian University Entrance Exam (Konkur) from University of Tehran

Certificate of Teaching Swim this certification was given in summer of 2017

Research Interests

.... Related Courses

- Machine Learning
- Artificial Intelligence
- Deep Learning
- Supervised Learning
- Speech Recognition
- Handwriting Recognition
- Bio-Computing
- NLP
- Data Mining

Deep learning currently studying
Statistical Methods currently studying
Artificial Intelligence 18/20
Bio-Computing 17.62/20

Programming 17.62/20 Programming 18.75/20 Data Mining 14.5/20 Linear Algebra 15.5/20 Probability 1 15/20

University Projects

Scientific calculationsImplemented of Bezier curves on a dataset of English handwriting for classification and recognition.

(by the help of one of my teachers in ML field)

Al Recognized pattern of some cancer cells

Natural Inspired Algorithms Developed a basic neural network

Data Mining Extracted some Association Rules and generated Classification on a dataset

Assembly Implemented a calculator with 4 main operations

Assembly Designed a Morris Mano basic computer in Logisim software

Advanced programming Created Tank game, system of ordering in cafe (both object oriented base) using Java

Languages of Programming Made Tic-tac-toe game with Rust

Basic programming Developed and deployed a website by Django

Work Experience

Developed a data analyzer app

for students of Alavi high school

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, Numpy), SQL Server, chart.js, Git
- Soft Skills: Problem Solving, Teamwork, Time Management, Communication

Developed a notification system

for SMS and Telegram

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), PostgresSQL, API and CRUD, Git
- · Soft Skills: Problem Solving, Time Management

Designed and developed an automation

for factory of ScarfBank

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), PostgresSQL, API and CRUD, Git
- Soft Skills: Agile, Pattern designing, Writing code structures, Problem Solving, Time Management, Communication

Developed and deployed Whatsapp engine

June 2022 - current

September 2020 - January 2021

February 2021 - August 2021

September 2021 - May 2022

for *Odoo* ERP

- Technical Skills: Python (Djnago, DRF), JS (fastify), API, Git
- Soft Skills: Pattern designing, Writing code structures, Problem Solving, Communication

Teaching Experience

- Tutor of Python programming for 6 month
- Tutor of Statistics and probability lesson for a bachelor student for 4 month
- · Tutor of Math for high school students for 4 month
- Tutor of Arabic for a high school student for 5 month

Skills

Programming:

- Python: Pandas, PyTorch, Tensorflow, NumPy, Django, DRF
- Java
- Assembly
- Rust
- R
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- SQL

Technical Skills:

- - -
- Linux

Git

- LaTeX
- Docker

Miscellaneous:

- Agile
- writing
- giving speech
- teaching
- playing tennis
- playing soccer

Languages

Persian Mother tongue

English IELTS currently studying. Expected to get minimum 7 out of 9

Arabic professional level in academic Arabic

Hobbies and Interests

programming solving enigmas and puzzles playing and watching Tennis playing Soccer reading researching watching movies

travelling with family and friends

Refrences

Name: Dr. Bagher BabaAli Email: babaali@ut.ac.ir

Location College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.

Name: Dr. Mojtaba Mojtahedi Email: mojtaba.mojtahedi@ut.ac.ir

Location College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.

Name: Dr. Hedieh Sajedi Email: hhsajedi@ut.ac.ir

Location College of Science / School of Mathematics, Statistics and Computer Science, University of Tehran, Tehran, Iran.